Bella@Drink! Drink! Drink!
You@OK
You@It's me instead
Bella@Okay, let me change you
You@Okay, I've never... kissed someone in an elevator.
You@Wow, bold much? Not even a little shy?
Bella@It's okay to kiss someone in the elevator
You@Okay, okay, then I'll continue
Bella@good
You@Well... think about it, I've never
You@field gun
You@Yeah, there's a show
You@Be honest
You@Wow wow wow wow
You@You had a very exciting time
Bella@No, no one keeps asking this question.
You@Ah, how did I know you have them? You’re so fierce.
Bella@Ah, no matter what, change me, change me, change me
You@OK, OK, you ask
Bella@I've never had
Bella@Calling your sex partner the wrong name